Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7 Locals, 2.
  - Local 750
    - Local 750 Incoming Correspondence, March 2, 1941-October 25, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Emspak to Motter Regarding Wage Policy, August 27, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Motter Regarding Strike, April 30, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Reamen Snyder Regarding Finances, January 18, 1949; 8.
      - Emspak to Delbert Wells Regarding Finances, June 23, 1949; 9.
      - Emspak to Daniel McGarvey Regarding Finances, June 29, 1949; 10.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, July 5, 1949; 11.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, July 18, 1949; 12.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, July 27, 1949; 13.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, August 2, 1949; 14.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, August 12, 1949; 15.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, August 17, 1949; 16.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, August 25, 1949; 17.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, August 30, 1949; 18.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, September 7, 1949; 19.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, September 27, 1949; 20.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, October 5, 1949; 21.
      - Emspak to Motter Regarding Finances, October 6, 1949; 22.
      - Emspak to McGarvey Regarding Finances, October 13, 1949; 23.
      - Emspak to Motter Regarding Finances, October 18, 1949; 24.
      - Emspak to Motter Regarding Finances, October 25, 1949; 25.
    - Local 750 Incoming Correspondence, October 29, 1941-April 6, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Julius Emspak to Delbert Wells Regarding Affidavits, November 2, 1949; 1.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, November 3, 1949; 2.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, November 7, 1949; 3.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, November 9, 1949; 4.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, November 15, 1949; 5.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, November 22, 1949; 6.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, November 29, 1949; 7.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, December 7, 1949; 8.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, December 14, 1949; 9.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, December 19, 1949; 10.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, December 28, 1949; 11.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, January 10, 1950; 12.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, January 18, 1950; 13.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, January 26, 1950; 14.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, February 3, 1950; 15.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, February 8, 1950; 16.
      - Emspak to Frank Motter Regarding Finances, February 10, 1950; 17.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, February 15, 1950; 18.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, February 21, 1950; 19.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, March 3, 1950; 20.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, March 27, 1950; 21.
      - Emspak to UE Locals Regarding Finances, March 28, 1950; 22.
      - Emspak to Riemenschneider Regarding Finances, April 6, 1950; 23.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Helen Jones Regarding Motion, October 6, 1941; 24.
      - James Matles to William Joseph Regarding Convention, October 29, 1941; 25.
      - A. Towsen to Harry Wolcott Regarding Finances, 26.
    - Local 750 Outgoing Correspondence, October 27, 1941-February 6, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Helen James to James Matles Regarding Staff Change, July 25, 1943; 1.
      - James to Julius Emspak Regarding Motion Questions, September 7, 1943; 2.
      - James to UE Regarding Officer List, January 10, 1944; 3.
      - James to Emspak Regarding Constitution, January 22, 1944; 4.
      - James to Emspak Regarding Address, January 22, 1944; 5.
      - James to Gentlemen Regarding Motion, 6.
      - William Joseph to Matles Regarding Plant Wages, October 27, 1941; 7.
      - William King to Emspak Regarding Membership, November 20, 1944; 8.
      - H. McElwain to Emspak Regarding Audit, October 19, 1942; 9.
      - Dan McGarvey to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Walkout, April 12, 1943; 10.
      - McGarvey to N. Pernice Regarding Motion, November 29, 1948; 11.
      - McGarvey to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Strike, July 21, 1949; 12.
      - McGarvey to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 16, 1949; 13.
      - McGarvey to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 20, 1949; 14.
      - McGarvey to UE Regarding Finances, October 6, 1949; 15.
      - McGarvey to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 6, 1950; 16.
      - McGarvey to UE Regarding Aid, 17.
      - McGarvey Letter Regarding Finances, 18.
      - McGarvey to Emspak Regarding Finances, 19.
      - Frank Motter to Emspak Regarding Officers List, January 27, 1942; 20.
      - Motter to Emspak Regarding Bonding, February 7, 1942; 21.
      - Motter to Emspak Regarding Charter, May 12, 1943; 22.
      - Motter to Emspak Regarding Audit, July 19, 1943; 23.
      - Motter to UE Regarding Wage Freeze, August 24, 1945; 24.
      - Motter to Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, May 1, 1946; 25.
    - Local 750 Outgoing Correspondence, February 15, 1942-March 21, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Frank Motter to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, April 30, 1947; 1.
      - Motter to Fitzgerald Regarding Strike, June 1, 1949; 2.
      - Motter to Julius Emspak Regarding Aid, September 26, 1949; 3.
      - Motter to Emspak Regarding Strike Progress, September 27, 1949; 4.
      - Motter to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 10, 1950; 5.
      - Motter to Local Members Regarding End of Strike, March 21, 1950; 6.
      - Motter to Emspak Regarding Charter, 7.
      - David Reamensnyder to UE Regarding Staff Condemnation, January 1946; 8.
      - Reamensnyder to Emspak Regarding Requested Information, December 1, 1949; 9.
      - Delbert Wells to James Matles Regarding Contract, February 15, 1942; 10.
      - Wells to Fitzgerald Regarding Labor Dispute, March 31, 1947; 11.
      - Harry Wolcott to David Ratner Regarding Finances, April 26, 1944; 12.
      - Wolcott to Townsend Regarding Finances, April 27, 1944; 13.
      - Staff Memo Regarding Bonding, October 6, 1947; 14.
    - Local 750 Bonding, February 19-24, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Local 750 Vouchers, March 11, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Local 750 Money Orders, October 27, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Local 750 Leaflet, "Christmas For Our Kids", December 6, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Local 750 Newspaper Clippings, January 9-11, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Taylor-Winfield, January 9, 1941; 1.
      - Taylor-Winfield Plant, January 11, 1941; 2.
    - Local 750 Separate Charters, April-May 1943 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Ray Klausner to Victor Decavitch, April 13, 1943; 1.
      - Homer Pierce Brief, May 1943; 2.
    - Local 750 Strike, April 25-May 22, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, April 25, 1946; 1.
      - Herbert Hirshberg to US Department of Labor, April 26, 1946; 2.
      - Hirshberg to UE, May 22, 1946; 3.
    - Local 750 Strike, July 29, 1949-April 20, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Herbert Hirshberg to Julius Emspak, July 29, 1949; 1.
      - Hirshberg to Emspak, August 23, 1949; 2.
      - O.J. Gould to UE Secretary-Treasurer, October 14, 1949; 3.
      - Emspak to Gould, October 17, 1949; 4.
      - E.A. Dewald to Emspak, March 6, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Hirshberg, March 8, 1950; 6.
      - Katherine Reamensyder to James Matles, March 14, 1950; 7.
      - Dewald to Emspak, March 15, 1950; 8.
      - Reamensyder to Emspak, March 22, 1950; 9.
      - Reamensyder to Matles, March 24, 1950; 10.
      - Hirshberg to David Ratner, April 3, 1950; 11.
      - Hirshberg to Matles, April 18, 1950; 12.
      - Matles to Gould, April 20, 1950; 13.
    - Local 750 Correspondence and Report, February 23, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Haug Regarding Per Capita, February 23, 1944; 1.
      - Organizers Report Excerpt Regarding Separate Charters, 2.
  - Local 751
    - Local 751 Officers Lists, February 1-March 9, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Local 751 Incoming Correspondence, January 8, 1941-December 11, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Joe Dermody to L. Horden Regarding Travel Plans, October 23, 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Harry Coates Regarding Materials, January 8, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Bonding, July 24, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Finances, October 31, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Grievances, November 7, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Convention, November 17, 1941; 6.
      - Emspak to John Snyder Regarding Bonding, February 13, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Snyder Regarding Constitution, March 5, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Snyder Regarding Constitution, April 8, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Contract, December 21, 1942; 10.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Contract, January 11, 1943; 11.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Negotiations, February 25, 1943; 12.
      - Emspak to Coates Regarding Executive Order, April 23, 1943; 13.
      - Emspak to S. Rader Regarding Finances, November 21, 1944; 14.
      - Emspak to Frank Conoy Regarding Bonding, December 11, 1946; 15.
      - Leo Jandreau to Coates Regarding Contract, September 8, 1943; 16.
      - Jandreau to Conoy Regarding Contract, December 14, 1943; 17.
      - James Matles to Coates Regarding Grievances, November 4, 1941; 18.
      - Matles to Coates Regarding Organization, November 12, 1941; 19.
      - Matles to Coates Regarding Meeting, December 30, 1941; 20.
      - Albert Olson to Coates Regarding Finances, July 16, 1941; 21.
    - Local 751 Outgoing Correspondence, January 1, 1941-March 3, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Harry Coates to Julius Emspak Regarding Wage Rates, January 1, 1941; 1.
      - Coates to James Matles Regarding Supplies, April 10, 1941; 2.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Bonding, July 21, 1941; 3.
      - Coates to Matles Regarding Grievances, November 1, 1941; 4.
      - Coates to Fred Haug Regarding Grievances, December 12, 1941; 5.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Contract, January 4, 1942; 6.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 28, 1942; 7.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, July 17, 1942; 8.
      - Coates to Matles, July 20, 1942; 9.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Grievances, February 15, 1943; 10.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Executive Order, April 13, 1943; 11.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Dues, May 14, 1943; 12.
      - Coates to Leo Jandreau Regarding Contract Printing, September 1, 1943; 13.
      - Coates to Jandreau Regarding Contract, September 20, 1943; 14.
      - Coates to Emspak Regarding Material, November 24, 1943; 15.
      - Frank Conroy to UE Regarding Contract, September 24, 1943; 16.
      - Thomas Cunningham to Emspak Regarding Staff Change, November 15, 1943; 17.
      - L. Horden to Joe Dermody Regarding Travel Plans, October 21, 1944; 18.
      - Merle Joseph to Emspak Regarding Grievances, November 13, 1941; 19.
      - Harold Minchen to Executive Board Regarding Commended Action, March 3, 1941; 20.
      - Georgia Quinlan to Emspak Regarding Officer Lists, January 26, 1943; 21.
      - Quinlan to Emspak Regarding Address, February 15, 1943; 22.
      - Quinlan to Emspak Regarding Contract, February 26, 1943; 23.
      - Sammy Rader to Harry Bradbury Regarding Wage Settlement, March 14, 1946; 24.
      - John Snyder to Emspak Regarding Constitution, February 13, 1942; 25.
      - Snyder to Emspak Regarding Ratification, June 22, 1942; 26.
    - Local 751 Bonding, April 23-27, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Local 751 Financial Report, March 8, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Local 751 Coates Letters, December 16, 1941-January 5, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - Fred Haug to Julius Emspak, December 16, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to Haug, January 5, 1942; 2.
    - Local 751 Niles, September 13, 1956-February 27, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Local 751 Niles General Electric and Niles Glass Works, October 16, 1968-February 22, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Local 751 Legislative Committee and Political Action, May 24, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Local 751 Corresponcence, June 10, 1941-May 13, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Julius Emspak to Fred Haug Regarding Per Capita, June 10, 1941; 1.
      - Arnold Pokki Case, December 1941; 2.
      - Harry Coates to James Matles Regarding Organization and Bridgeville General Electric with Bridgeville Glass Works, November 1, 1941; 3.
      - Grievences Regarding Overtime, February 3, 1943; 4.
      - Proposed Dues Collection Routine, May 13, 1943; 5.
  - Local 752
    - Local 752 Correspondence, September 25, 1940-March 10, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Charter Application, September 25, 1940; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Arthur Garfield, March 10, 1941; 2.
  - Local 753
    - Local 753 Constitution, December 12, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Local 753 Officers Minutes, January 2-December 29, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Local 753 Incoming Correspondence, May 2, 1941-February 2, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Julius Emspak to Robert Galligan Regarding Bonding, May 2, 1941; 1.
      - Emspak to K. Kirkendall Regarding Finances, September 11, 1941; 2.
      - Emspak to Eugene Jacobs Regarding Finances, October 12, 1941; 3.
      - Emspak to Galligan Regarding Recieved Letter, November 17, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Galligan Regarding Constitution, December 15, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to William Tootle Regarding Finances, February 2, 1942; 6.
      - James Matles to Matinell Ambrose Regarding Amalgamation, January 14, 1942; 7.
      - Matles to UE Regarding Negotiations, June 21, 1941; 8.
      - Matles to Galligan Regarding Supplies, August 18, 1941; 9.
    - Local 753 Outgoing Correspondence, March 26-December 31, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Anthony Ambrose to UE Regarding Publications, August 10, 1941; 1.
      - Marinell Ambrose to James Matles Regarding Minutes, December 31, 1941; 2.
      - Robert Galligan to Julius Emspak Regarding Bonding, May 8, 1941; 3.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Bonding, March 26, 1941; 4.
      - Galligan to Matles Regarding Supplies, August 16, 1941; 5.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Strike Finances, September 15, 1941; 6.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 8, 1941; 7.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Constitution, November 15, 1941; 8.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Constitution, December 3, 1941; 9.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 8, 1941; 10-11.
      - Galligan to Emspak Regarding Constitution, December 11, 1941; 12.
      - Eugene Jacobs to Emspak Regarding Aid, August 29, 1941; 13.
      - Jacobs to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 1, 1941; 14.
      - Jacobs to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 24, 1941; 15.
      - Joseph Kavalauskas to Matles Regarding Wage Rates, December 11, 1941; 16.
      - John Thomas to Matles Regarding Agreement, October 13, 1941; 17.
    - Local 753 Bonding, December 9, 1940-July 1, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Local 753 Financial Reports, January 1, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Local 753 Newspaper Clipping, "National Labor Relations Board Ballot Protested", March 6, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Local 753-806 Merger, December 29, 1941-January 15, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Local 753-806 Consolidating Committee Meeting Minutes, December 29, 1941; 1.
      - Local 753-806 Consolidating Committee Meeting Minutes, January 2, 1942; 2.
      - Local 753-806 Consolidation Banquet Meeting Minutes, January 8, 1942; 3.
      - Local 753 Special Meeting Minutes, January 15, 1942; 4.
      - Articles of Amalgamation, January 9, 1942; 5.
      - Consolidating Committee Minutes, January 9, 1942; 6.
    - Local 753 Correspondence, June 30-September 22, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Chrysler Corporation to Local 753 Regarding Wages, June 30, 1941; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Arthur Garfield Regarding Strike, September 22, 1941; 2.
  - Local 754
    - Local 754 Officers Lists, October 26, 1942-April 27, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Local 754 Constitution, December 15, 1941-November 11, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Local 754 Officers Resolution, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Local 754 Membership Resolution, April 3, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Local 754 Incoming Correspondence, October 3, 1941-May 9, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Janet Barish to Ernest Block Regarding Finances, January 5, 1945; 1.
      - Barish to Mary Cross Regarding Finances, November 10, 1949; 2.
      - William Cahn to Chas Sims Regarding Material, March 18, 1949; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to R. Davis Regarding Constitution, February 23, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Ernest Black Regarding Insurance, March 5, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Black Regarding Resolution, September 24, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Sims Regarding Membership, January 19, 1944; 7.
      - Emspak to Charles Marcum Regarding Supplies, March 20, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to Marcum Regarding Fees, June 27, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to Anita Quinn Regarding Fees, February 6, 1946; 10.
      - Emspak to Lloyd Garddok Regarding Stewards List, June 4, 1947; 11.
      - Emspak to Sims Regarding Bargaining, December 11, 1947; 12.
      - Emspak to Marcum Regarding Convention, November 8, 1948; 13.
      - Emspak to Marcum Regarding Charter, December 21, 1949; 14.
      - Emspak to Sims Regarding Officers Information, April 20, 1955; 15.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Robert Harrison Regarding Constitution, December 10, 1943; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to Sims Regarding Stewards Classes, March 25, 1947; 17.
      - Fitzgerald to Virginia Hipple Regarding Wage Conference, April 21, 1954; 18.
      - Fitzgerald to Sims Regarding Election, 19.
      - James Matles to Viola Staff Regarding Conference, October 3, 1941; 20.
      - Matles to Marcum Regarding Meeting, November 5, 1948; 21.
      - Matles to Sims Regarding Meeting, December 26, 1950; 22.
      - Matles to Sims Regarding Grievances, March 5, 1953; 23.
      - Matles to Hipple Regarding Finances, November 2, 1953; 24.
      - Matles to Hipple Regarding Finances, November 9, 1953; 25.
      - Matles to Sims Regarding Strike, May 2, 1956; 26.
      - Matles to Sims Regarding Finances, May 9, 1956; 27.
      - William Snoots to Marcum Regarding Candidates Support, March 2, 1949; 28.
    - Local 754 Outgoing Correspondence, February 19, 1942-April 29, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Charles Bell to Franklin Roosevelt Regarding War Production, October 11, 1944; 1.
      - Ernest Black to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, February 19, 1942; 2.
      - Black to James Matles Regarding Contract, March 21, 1942; 3.
      - Black to Emspak Regarding Staff Changes, July 23, 1942; 4.
      - Wallace Combs to Emspak Regarding Resolution, February 6, 1950; 5.
      - Combs to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations, January 12, 1951; 6.
      - R. Davis to Emspak Regarding By-Laws, February 19, 1942; 7.
      - James Ferguson to Emspak Regarding Audit, August 12, 1952; 8.
      - Robert Harrison to Fitzgerald Regarding Motion, December 2, 1943; 9.
      - Virginia Hipple to Matles Regarding Stewards Classes, February 1, 1952; 10.
      - Hipple to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting, August 12, 1953; 11.
      - Hipple to Fitzgerald Regarding Resolution, April 14, 1954; 12.
      - Hipple to Matles Regarding Personal Affairs, April 29, 1955; 13.
      - Charles Marcum to Emspak Regarding Fees, June 19, 1945; 14.
      - Marcum to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 19, 1947; 15.
      - Marcum to Local Members Regarding Meeting, December 10, 1947; 16.
      - Marcum to Emspak Regarding Travel Plans, July 22, 1948; 17.
      - Marcum to Emspak Regarding Meeting, November 1, 1948; 18.
      - Marcum to Elbert Thomas Regarding Wagner Act Support, February 8, 1949; 19.
      - Marcum to William Snoots Regarding Publicity Condemnation, February 25, 1949; 20.
      - Marcum to Emspak Regarding Charter, December 7, 1949; 21.
      - Marcum to D. Warner Regarding Contract Violation, March 20, 1952; 22.
      - Marcum to Warner Regarding Proposal, June 5, 1952; 23.
      - Marcum to Local 754 Members Regarding Resignation, 24.
      - Rose Milholland to Bill Cahn Regarding Publicity, August 18, 1949; 25.
    - Local 754 Outgoing Correspondence, November 25, 1942-April 30, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Ralph Pearson to Julius Emspak Regarding Election, February 4, 1943; 1.
      - Anita Quinn to Emspak Regarding Fee Waiver, January 25, 1946; 2.
      - Robert Raines to Carol Grey Regarding Finances, January 27, 1956; 3.
      - Raines to Grey Regarding Finances, February 22, 1956; 4.
      - Raines to Grey Regarding Finances, March 15, 1956; 5.
      - Raines to Grey Regarding Finances, April 30, 1956; 6.
      - Charles Sims to James Matles Regarding Contract, April 8, 1943; 7.
      - Sims to Matles Regarding Publications, April 9, 1943; 8.
      - Sims to Emspak Regarding Election, September 23, 1943; 9-10.
      - Sims to Emspak Regarding Membership List, January 15, 1944; 11.
      - Sims to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Stewards Classes, February 24, 1947; 12.
      - Sims to Emspak Regarding Contract, December 3, 1947; 13.
      - Sims to Fitzgerald Regarding Election, September 9, 1948; 14.
      - Sims to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 9, 1949; 15.
      - Robert Strader to Fitzgerald Regarding Constitution, November 25, 1942; 16.
      - UE Local 754 to David Ratner Regarding Meeting, September 25, 1952; 17.
    - Local 754 Bonding, April 10, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Local 754 Supply Request, March 5, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Local 754 Finances, June 24, 1945, October 11, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Receipt, October 11, 1954; 1.
      - Delinquency Notice, June 25, 1945; 2.
    - Local 754 Leaflets, June 6, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - "Action - Protect Your Union", 1.
      - "1948 - Goal for Local 754", 2.
      - "Membership Says We Want A Wage Increase Now", 3.
      - "A Stab in the Back", 4.
      - "Election Day", 5.
      - Officers List, 6-7.
      - Election Results, 1950; 8.
      - Election Ballot, 9.
      - Contract Changes, July 6, 1953; 10.
      - "Master Electric Workers Say 'Who Sold Out'", 11.
      - UE Special Notice, 12.
      - "Fighting Committee Organized", 13.
    - Local 754 Health Insurance, February 2-13, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - K. M. Kirkendall to Julius Emspak, February 2, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Kirkendall, February 13, 1942; 2.
    - Local 754 Correspondence and Finances, 1937-1953 (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - Charter Application, August 26, 1937; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Arthur Garfield Regarding Officers, April 15, 1941; 2.
      - Grant McGlothin to Emspak Regarding Officers, May 28, 1942; 3.
      - Victor Decavitch to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 9, 1942; 4.
      - Ella Gardner to Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, May 28, 1951; 5.
      - David Ratner Memo, August 13, 1952; 6.
      - Sterling Neal to Emspak Regarding Harvester Strike, March 20, 1953; 7.
      - Financial Facts Regarding Per Capita, 1953; 8.
      - Ella Gardner to James Matles Regarding Education, 9.
  - Local 755
    - Local 755 Constitution and By-Laws, August 17, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Local 755 Constitution, October 23, 1942-January 12, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - Local 755 Officers Lists, January 5, 1941-April 6, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - Local 755 Membership Resolution, June 24, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 77)